{
    "id": "e7635bdf89774be7993db5af550afa41",
    "title": "Prepositional Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather have coffee …………………… tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "instead of",
                "instead from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0734fb73cd45411b8efe58a9571f1246"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… the rains, we went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite of",
                "In spite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f97408a9b434116b799b49f2915ffbf"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… fire, break glass to escape.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In case of",
                "In case",
                "In case with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "94e672392b8c4357bde81965e4743f18"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am standing here ……………………… my friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in behalf of",
                "on behalf of",
                "on behalf"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "23502d6712e24712a152ad41bf7ea043"
        },
        {
            "question": "We solved the problem …………………. a new device developed by our engineers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by means of",
                "by means",
                "by means to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "77286851113f4e36835dfa6a7c9be188"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….., I had a happy childhood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "On the whole",
                "In the whole",
                "By the whole"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "99420701cde24ecd81e06390777fc4f5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you help me …………………… .?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in anyway",
                "any way",
                "in any way"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4e6a3e49179144ada0c034a19bfb0acd"
        },
        {
            "question": "She didn’t allow cancer to discourage her. ……………………, she began to work twice as hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "On the contrary",
                "By the contrary",
                "In the contrary"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff515b01edf64e4f837d6de953fd9fa7"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………, we are impressed with her performance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In general",
                "On general",
                "By general"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5324cf5af2af48518adc1221ef628725"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am seeing him in May – ………………….. in June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "or rather",
                "in rather"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "95d6d59c78934b50a8856191d69b3ebb"
        }
    ]
}